<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:54:17 +0000</pubDate><title><![CDATA[terms]]></title><url><![CDATA[terms]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[terms]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><content><![CDATA[<p>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;html&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;head&gt;</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &lt;title&gt;Terms &amp; Conditions&lt;/title&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="style.css"&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;/head&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;body class="terms"&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome to learning ladders&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;p&gt;About the WebsiteWelcome to www.learning ladder.com (Website).</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; The Website provides you with anopportunity to browse and purchase various products that have been listed for</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; salethrough the Website (Products). The Website provides this service by way of granting youaccess</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; to the content on the Website (Purchase Services).The Website is operated by Learning Ladder Pty</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; Ltd.Access to and use of the Website,</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; or any of its associated Products or Services, isprovided by Learning Ladder Pty Ltd.</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; Please read these terms and conditions (Terms)carefully.</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;By using, browsing and/or reading the Website, this signifies that you have read,</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;understood and agree to be bound by the Terms. If you do not agree with the Terms,</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;youmust cease usage of the Website, or any of Services,</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;immediately.Learning Ladder Pty Ltd reserves the right to review and change any of the Terms byupdating this page at its sole discretion.</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;When Learning Ladder Pty Ltd updates the Terms,it will use reasonable endeavours to provide you with notice of updates to the Terms.</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Anychanges to the Terms take immediate effect from the date of their publication. Before youcontinue, we recommend you keep a copy of the Terms for your records&lt;/p&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;h3&gt;Acceptance of the Terms&lt;/h3&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;p&gt;You accept the Terms by remaining on the Website.</p>

<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; You may also accept the Terms by clicking toaccept or agree to the Terms where this option is made available to you by Learning Ladder PtyLtd in the user interface&lt;/p&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;h3&gt;Privacy&lt;/h3&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;p&gt;Learning Ladder Pty Ltd takes your privacy seriously and any information provided through youruse of the Website and/or the Purchase Services are subject to Learning Ladder Pty Ltd'sPrivacy Policy, which is available on the Website.&lt;/p&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;h3&gt;Governing Law&lt;/h3&gt;</p>

<p>&lt;p&gt;The Terms are governed by the laws of New South Wales, Australia. Any dispute, controversy,proceeding or claim of whatever nature arising out of or in any way relating to the Terms and therights created hereby shall be governed, interpreted and construed by, under and pursuant to thelaws of New South Wales Australia, without reference to conflict of law principles,notwithstanding mandatory rules. The validity of this governing law clause is not contested. TheTerms shall be binding to the benefit of the parties hereto and their successors and assigns.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private><author><![CDATA[ezaz]]></author></item>
